David Grasmann

Head of Business Development DACH at SentiOne

Summary

Experienced Business Development Manager with a demonstrated history of working in the service industry. Skilled in Business Development, Marketing, Social Listening, Online Marketing, and Social CRM. Strong sales professional with a Diplom focused in Business Law from Hochschule für Technik und Wirtschaft Berlin.

Experience

Head of Business Development DACH at SentiOne April 2017 - Present

SentiOne is the Number One Social Listening focused on Europe. Everyday we work with over 500 brands on 26 European markets.

We help global and local brands track and measure consumers opinions and activities in social media.

We work with over one five hundred large and medium companies: Procter&Gamble, McDonald's, Nike, Unilever, Beiersdorf, Tesco, Starcom, Mindshare, Mediacom or Saatchi&Saatchi.

Every day we help our customers:

- monitor their brands online
- track social media KPIs
- collect real-time consumer insights
- measure reach of online campaigns
- control their online reputation
- improve online customer care
- identify brand ambassadors
- detect negative mentions
- boost online sales by finding potential leads

We're the only Social Listening Company able to deliver instant local data from 26 European markets:

Germany, Austria, Switzerland, Netherlands, Belgium, Denmark, Sweden, Norway, Finland, Poland, Russia, Ukraine, Czech Republic, Slovakia, Hungary, Greece, Slovenia, Romania, Lithuania, Latvia, Estonia, Bulgaria, Serbia, Croatia, Montenegro and Bosnia&Herzegovina.

Business Development Manager August 2015 - March 2017 (1 year 8 months)

Senior Account Manager at Brunel May 2012 - July 2015 (3 years 3 months)

Account Manager at Brunel
September 2010 - April 2012 (1 year 8 months)

Education

Hochschule für Technik und Wirtschaft Berlin Diplom, Business Law, 2006 - 2010 EAE Business School International Business, 2009 - 2009

David Grasmann

Head of Business Development DACH at SentiOne



Contact David on LinkedIn